Uneku Ogbaje

Web Developer

19 Olumide Odusola Street, Awoyaya, Lagos. (+234) 8140086240 unekuogbaje@gmail.com

PROFILE

A sales professional who has spent two years gaining valuable skills in the tech space. I have a great passion for front-end design and development, which drove me to take advantage of several learning resources and begin my transition into tech when the Covid pandemic struck in 2020. I'm teachable, adaptable, and highly empathetic towards product users and their needs, and I love to create thoughtful, beautiful, and simple things that make lives easier. I'm a lifetime learner and remain committed to achieving mutual growth wherever I find myself.

EXPERIENCE

Tele-Sales Agent - Crowdyvest

Sept. 2021 - Date

- Reach out to customers informing them of products & promotions.
- Meet monthly targets
- Maintain customer database

Customer Success Executive/NYSC Staff - RealtyPros Investment IGL

Aug. 2019 - Sept.2020

- Develop and maintain good customer relationship
- Advice customers on products and services to purchase
- Work closely with customers to ensure satisfaction with products
- Improve products & services based on customer feedback

Senior Sales Associate/Beauty Adviser - HealthPlus Limited

Mar. 2018 - Aug. 2019

- Training and onboarding of new staff
- Handle change in policies and renewals
- Ensure appropriate & timely delivery of reports

CAREER ACHIEVEMENTS

 Began my transition to the tech space during the 2020 pandemic, utilizing tools like freeCodeCamp, YouTube, Udemy & Zero to mastery academy.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF JOS

B.Ed Geography

2011 - 2016

GOOGLE UX DESIGN CERTIFICATE

Jan. 2022-Jul. 2022

ZERO TO MASTERY ACADEMY

Complete React Developer Course

Dec. 2021-Jun. 2022

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React(JS)

User Experience Design

Wireframing (Figma)

HOBBIES

Music, Travel & Art

LANGUAGES

English

Hausa